<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">QuasistR</string>
    <string name="game_mode">Game Mode</string>
    <string name="select_deck">Select a Deck</string>
    <string name="play_game">PLAY GAME</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings &amp; Info</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="normal_mode">Normal</string>
    <string name="challenge_mode">Challenge</string>
    <string name="language_learning_mode">Language Learning</string>
    <string name="guessed_words">GUESSED WORDS</string>
    <string name="skipped_words">SKIPPED WORDS</string>
    <string name="perfect_score">PERFECT SCORE!</string>
    <string name="game_results">GAME RESULTS</string>
    <string name="play_again">PLAY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="menu">MENU</string>
    <string name="tilt_up_correct">Tilt UP when you guess correctly</string>
    <string name="tilt_down_skip">Tilt DOWN to skip</string>
    <string name="words">words</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="about_quasistr">About QuasistR</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="follow_on_instagram">Follow on Instagram</string>
    <string name="contact_support">Contact Support</string>
    <string name="rate_quasistr">Rate QuasistR</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming soon</string>
    <string name="sound_effects">Sound Effects</string>
    <string name="vibration">Vibration</string>
    <string name="selected">selected</string>
    <string name="ui_language">Menu Language</string>
    <string name="deck_language">Game Content Language</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select Language</string>
    <string name="game_settings">GAME SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="language_settings">LANGUAGE SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="about">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="legal">LEGAL</string>
    <string name="connect">CONNECT</string>
    <string name="end_game_title">End Game?</string>
    <string name="end_game_message">Are you sure you want to end the current game?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="get_ready">Get Ready!</string>
    <string name="starting_in">Starting in...</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="normal_mode_description">60 seconds to guess as many words as possible</string>
    <string name="challenge_mode_description">Get +10 seconds for each correct guess, -5 seconds for each skip</string>
    <string name="language_learning_description">Learn vocabulary in German, English, or Hungarian</string>
    <string name="pvp_team_mode">PVP Team</string>
    <string name="pvp_team_description">Team vs Team competition mode</string>
    <string name="press_back_again_to_exit">Press back again to exit</string>
    <string name="guessed">GUESSED</string>
    <string name="skipped">SKIPPED</string>
    <string name="accuracy">ACCURACY</string>
    <string name="no_words_guessed">No words guessed</string>
    <string name="no_words_skipped">No words skipped</string>
    <string name="perfect_score_message">You guessed all %1$d words correctly!</string>
    <string name="about_description">Learn about the game</string>
    <string name="credits_description">Development team</string>
    <string name="terms_description">Privacy policy &amp; terms</string>
    <string name="rate_description">Rate us on Google Play</string>
    <string name="developer_credit">Developed by Adam Miko</string>
    <string name="designer_credit">Graphic design by Gia Phan</string>
    <string name="about_content">QuasistR is the ultimate charades game for your phone! Hold your device to your forehead and let others act out the word on screen.\n\n• Tilt UP when you guess correctly\n• Tilt DOWN to skip the word\n• Choose from various themed decks\n• Perfect for parties and gatherings\n\nHave fun and enjoy the game!</string>
    <string name="select_target_language">Select Target Language</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="word_count">%1$d words</string>
    <string name="correct">Correct</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>

    <string name="terms_content">TERMS OF SERVICE and PRIVACY POLICY\n\nLast updated: June 1, 2025\n\nIMPORTANT—PLEASE READ CAREFULLY: By downloading, installing, or using QuasistR (the “App”), you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service (“Terms”) and our Privacy Policy (together, the “Agreement”). If you do not agree to all of these Terms, do not use the App.\n\n1. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS  \n   a. These Terms constitute a legally binding agreement between you (“User,” “you,” or “your”) and the developer of this App (“we,” “us,” or “our”).  \n   b. By accessing or using the App (including all features, content, and services), you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these Terms and our Privacy Policy, found below.  \n   c. If you are using the App on behalf of an organization, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to bind that organization to these Terms.\n\n2. ELIGIBILITY  \n   a. You must be at least 13 years old to use the App. If you are between 13 and the age of majority in your jurisdiction, you represent that you have parental or legal guardian consent to use the App.  \n   b. If you are under 18, your parent or legal guardian must agree to these Terms on your behalf.\n\n3. LICENSE and RESTRICTIONS  \n   a. Subject to your compliance with these Terms, we grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to download, install, and use the App on a single device owned or controlled by you.  \n   b. You agree not to:  \n      i.  Reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, or otherwise attempt to derive the source code of the App;  \n      ii. Modify, adapt, translate, or create derivative works of the App;  \n      iii. Rent, lease, lend, sell, redistribute, or sublicense the App;  \n      iv. Use the App to violate any applicable law, regulation, or third-party rights;  \n      v. Use any automated means (e.g., robots, scrapers) to access or collect data from the App except as expressly permitted in writing;  \n      vi. Remove or alter any proprietary notices or labels in the App.\n\n4. USER OBLIGATIONS and CONDUCT  \n   a. You agree to use the App only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms.  \n   b. You are solely responsible for any content you generate, submit, or transmit through the App (if applicable). You agree not to upload, post, email, or otherwise transmit any unlawful, threatening, defamatory, obscene, or infringing content.  \n   c. We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your access to the App if you violate these Terms or engage in harmful or illegal behavior.\n\n5. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY  \n   a. All rights, title, and interest in and to the App (including but not limited to all code, design, text, graphics, interfaces, and sounds) and all intellectual property rights therein are and remain the exclusive property of the developer or its licensors.  \n   b. You acknowledge that you have no ownership rights in the App, and these Terms do not grant you any rights or licenses other than those expressly set forth herein.  \n   c. Any trademarks, service marks, graphics, or logos used in connection with the App are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.  \n   d. This App includes unlicensed use of Disney movie titles, celebrity names, and other copyrighted or trademarked content solely for entertainment under “fair use” principles. No rights to those titles, characters, or trademarks are granted. You agree to hold us harmless for such uses to the fullest extent permitted by law.\n\n6. THIRD-PARTY CONTENT  \n   a. The App may reference or link to third-party websites, services, or content (“Third-Party Content”). All Third-Party Content is provided solely as a convenience, and we do not endorse, warrant, or assume responsibility for any Third-Party Content.  \n   b. You acknowledge that fair use provisions (e.g., for parody, commentary, or critique) may apply to third-party titles or characters used within the App, and you agree we do not endorse or claim any ownership of those third-party rights.\n\n7. PRIVACY and DATA COLLECTION  \n   a. We respect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is incorporated herein by reference. In summary:  \n      i.  We collect only anonymous usage analytics and crash reports via Google Firebase’s free-tier services (Crashlytics, Performance Monitoring). We do not collect any personally identifiable information (PII), such as names, email addresses, phone numbers, or device identifiers beyond anonymized Firebase instance IDs.  \n      ii. We do not display ads or require any user registration or login.  \n      iii. Firebase (as a data processor) may have access to anonymized event and crash-log data. We do not receive any PII from Firebase.  \n      iv. You may disable analytics by turning off analytics permissions or opting out from Firebase Analytics in your device settings; however, doing so may limit our ability to detect and fix crashes.  \n      v.  We do not share any personal data with third parties, except that Firebase may process anonymized data under its own privacy policy.  \n   b. By using the App, you consent to the collection and use of data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.\n\n8. WARRANTY DISCLAIMER  \n   a. THE APP IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE,” and “WITH ALL FAULTS,” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES—EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY, OR OTHERWISE—INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, and NON-INFRINGEMENT.  \n   b. WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT (i) THE APP WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (ii) THE APP WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE, OR (iii) ANY DEFECTS OR ERRORS WILL BE CORRECTED.  \n   c. YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE APP.\n\n9. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY  \n   a. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL WE, OUR AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE APP, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.  \n   b. IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR AGGREGATE LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS OR YOUR USE OF THE APP EXCEED FIFTY EUROS (EUR 50) OR THE AMOUNT YOU PAID (IF ANY) TO DOWNLOAD OR USE THE APP, WHICHEVER IS LESS.\n\n10. INDEMNIFICATION  \n   You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless us and our officers, directors, employees, and agents from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, losses, and expenses (including reasonable attorneys’ fees) arising out of or in any way connected with (a) your access to or use of the App; (b) your violation of these Terms; © your infringement of any third-party rights; or (d) any User Content you submit.\n\n11. MODIFICATIONS TO THE TERMS OR APP  \n   a. We reserve the right to modify these Terms at any time. If we make material changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice within the App.  \n   b. Your continued use of the App after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms.  \n   c. We reserve the right to modify, suspend, or discontinue the App (or any part thereof) at any time without prior notice or liability.\n\n12. TERMINATION  \n   a. We may terminate or suspend your access to the App immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including if you breach these Terms.  \n   b. Upon termination, all provisions of these Terms which by their nature should survive will survive, including ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnification, and limitations of liability.\n\n13. GOVERNING LAW and JURISDICTION  \n   a. These Terms and any disputes arising out of or relating to the App or these Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Federal Republic of Germany (Germany), without regard to conflict-of-law principles.  \n   b. Any legal action or proceeding arising out of or related to these Terms or the App shall be brought exclusively in the courts of Berlin, Germany, and you irrevocably consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such courts.\n\n14. DISPUTE RESOLUTION and ARBITRATION  \n   a. Informal Resolution. In the event of any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to these Terms or the App, you agree to first contact us at quasistr@gmail.com and attempt to resolve the matter informally.  \n   b. Binding Arbitration. If we are unable to resolve the dispute informally within thirty (30) days, either party may submit the dispute to final, binding arbitration under the rules of the German Institution of Arbitration (Deutsche Institution für Schiedsgerichtsbarkeit, DIS).  \n      i. The arbitration shall be conducted in Berlin and in the English language.  \n      ii. The arbitrator’s award shall be final and binding, and judgment on the award may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction.\n\n15. SEVERABILITY  \n   If any provision of these Terms is found to be unlawful, void, or unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, and the remaining provisions shall remain in full force and effect.\n\n16. ENTIRE AGREEMENT  \n   These Terms, together with our Privacy Policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and us regarding the App and supersede all prior or contemporaneous agreements, understandings, or communications (written or oral).\n\n17. NOTICES  \n   All notices required or permitted under these Terms shall be in writing and sent to quasistr@gmail.com. Notices will be deemed given when received by us.\n\n18. CONTACT INFORMATION  \n   If you have any questions, concerns, or feedback about these Terms, the App, or the Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  \n   quasistr@gmail.com\n\nPRIVACY POLICY (INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE)  \nWe respect your privacy. This Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use the App.\n\n1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT  \n   a. Firebase Analytics and Crashlytics: We collect anonymous usage data and crash reports via Google Firebase’s free-tier services (Crashlytics, Performance Monitoring). This data helps us identify bugs, improve stability, and optimize performance.  \n   b. Device Identifiers: We may collect anonymized instance IDs assigned by Firebase. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.  \n   c. No Registration, No Ads: We do not require any user registration or login, and we do not display advertisements.  \n   d. Optional Information: If you choose to contact us via email, you provide us with your email address and any information included in your message. We use that information solely to respond to your inquiry.\n\n2. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION  \n   a. To Improve the App: Aggregated analytics help us identify bugs, optimize performance, and enhance features.  \n   b. To Communicate: If you email us, we may use your email address to respond to your inquiries.  \n   c. To Detect Abuse: Anonymous data may be used to monitor for suspicious activity or misuse.\n\n3. SHARING YOUR INFORMATION  \n   a. Firebase (Data Processor): We share anonymous analytics data with Firebase solely to provide crash reporting and performance analytics. Firebase’s own terms and privacy controls apply to that data.  \n   b. Legal Requirements: We may disclose personal information if required by law or to protect our legal rights.  \n   c. No Third-Party Marketing: We do not share or sell any user data for marketing or advertising purposes.\n\n4. DATA RETENTION  \n   We retain anonymous analytics data only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes described above. If you request deletion of any personal information (e.g., your email), we will remove it from our records when feasible.\n\n5. YOUR RIGHTS (GDPR and OTHER APPLICABLE LAWS)  \n   a. Access and Deletion: You may contact us at quasistr@gmail.com to request access to, correction of, or deletion of any personal information you have provided.  \n   b. Opt-Out: You can disable analytics collection by removing analytics permissions or opting out via your device settings.  \n   c. Complaint: If you believe your rights under applicable data protection laws have been violated, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction.\n\n6. DATA SECURITY  \n   We implement commercially reasonable security measures to protect data from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure. However, no transmission over the internet is 100% secure.\n\n7. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY  \n   The App is not intended for children under 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under 13. If we become aware we have collected personal data from a child under 13, we will delete it immediately.\n\n8. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  \n   We may update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you by posting the new policy in the App. The effective date will be updated. Your continued use after changes constitutes acceptance.\n\n9. CONTACT US  \n   If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, contact:  \n   quasistr@gmail.com\n</string>

    <string name="random_deck">Random Deck</string>
    <string name="surprise_me">Surprise me!</string>
    <string name="search_decks">Search decks...</string>

</resources>